Download our VPN application

Privacy policy
==============

Updated on: 2024-03-06

By visiting our websites and by accessing, installing and/or using the application, you confirm that you agree to our Privacy Policy. This article helps you to understand what information we collect, what we don’t collect, and how we collect, use, and store information.

### What information we collect on our website

Our website collects access logs (IP address, browser type, operating system) to operate our services and ensure their secure and reliable performance.

### Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your web browser on your computer's hard drive. A cookie file can contain information that the site uses to recognize something about you (such as your login name, or whether you've been to this site before or not). A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. The only personal information a cookie contains is the information you provide yourself.

### What information we collect on our application

We prioritize your privacy and security, collecting only anonymized data that cannot be used to identify you. This data collection is solely for the purpose of enhancing our service, ensuring you receive the best possible experience without compromising your privacy. We guarantee that this information is not shared with any third parties and is automatically deleted after 14 days for your peace of mind.

Data we collect includes:

* Your connection IP
* Application version
* The country from which you are connecting
* Your device's language setting
* Source of installation

With your explicit consent, we may also collect optional data such as:

* Your operating system version
* Device model
* Google Analytics data
* Crash reports

Please note, certain session-specific data like network settings, screen size, orientation or other data can be processed to optimize your experience but are not retained beyond your session.

For users who choose to create an account, we store your email and password securely. These are kept safely for as long as you wish to use our service. Remember, you have full control over your data and can delete your account at any time directly through the app. We are committed to ensuring your digital experience is both safe and satisfying, without ever compromising your privacy.

### Third party advertisers

In order to offer our VPN service for free to users without a subscription, we display advertisements. These ads are sourced from Google AdMob and ironSource Ltd. . For information about what data Google AdMob and ironSource Ltd. collect, please refer to the [Google Play data disclosure](https://developers.google.com/admob/android/privacy/play-data-disclosure#data_collected_and_shared_automatically) and [ironSource Ltd. Privacy Policy](https://developers.is.com/ironsource-mobile/air/ironsource-mobile-privacy-policy/) .

### What information we do not collect on our application

We want you to know that your privacy is our top priority. That's why we don't collect or store any details about your browsing history, what content you connect to, your IP addresses, when you browse, how much data you use, or even your DNS queries. In fact, we keep absolutely no logs of your browsing activities. And when we say no personal information is collected, we mean it! Your privacy and trust are super important to us.

And that's not all – we also promise not to share, sell, rent, or barter any identifiable personal information to any third party, in any way. Your information is yours alone.

Moreover, we're committed to keeping your information safe. Whether it's data collected through our website or app, we make sure it's protected, both online and offline. Rest assured, we're taking every precaution to guard your privacy.

Get the most out of your online experience, download Octohide now, and stay safe.

A better way to internet safety and security

[+370 600 29475](tel:+37060029475)[\[email protected\]](https://octohide.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

© 2024 Octohide. All Rights Reserved.
